

# USMAN HAMID

Mern Stack Developer

## CONTACT

**\** 0334-5885246

in linkedin.com/in/usmanhamid379

□ usmanhamid379@gmail.com

Range road, Rawalpindi

## **SKILLS**

#### **FRONTEND**

- Tailwind
- JavaScript
- react.js
- next.js
- redux
- toolkit
- rtkquery

#### **BACKEND**

- Node.js
- express.js
- nest.js
- postgresql
- mongodb
- prisma

### **PROFILE**

I am an accomplished and adaptable full-stack developer that has a love for creating user-focused and creative websites.

With a track record of providing flawless digital experiences, I have knowledge in both frontend and backend technologies. My ability to code, solve problems, and work in a collaborative team environment allows me to develop reliable and scalable solutions that promote corporate success.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **COMSATS UNIVERSITY**

Bachelors in Computer Science 2017-2021

#### MODEL SCIENCE COLLEGE RAWLAKOT

**FSC** 

2013-2014

## WORK EXPERIENCE

## June 2022-Present

Codeexperts

## **Full Stack Developer**

I orchestrated the end-to-end development of a robust e-commerce platform using my expertise in React, Node.js, and MongoDB. Collaborated effectively with cross-functional teams, utilizing strong communication skills to translate business requirements into scalable and responsive solutions.

## Jan 2022-May 2022

anticus PVT

Lanticus PVT LTD

## Front-end developer

I crafted visually stunning and responsive user interfaces, employing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to elevate the overall user experience.

Implemented innovative design solutions. Collaborated seamlessly with UX/UI teams, honing my skills in responsive design and ensuring a seamless integration of visual elements into the web applications

Potfolio: <a href="https://portfolio-usmanhamid.vercel.app">https://portfolio-usmanhamid.vercel.app</a>